## Isaiah Colson

colson.isaiah@gmail.com (505) 803-8182

isaiahcolson.com, github/isaiah, linkedin/isaiah

I'm a software engineer and designer and I specialize in front end development. I have been working in creative teams for the last 4 years creating videos and graphics for social media, live presentations, print, and web. Now I have focused on creating and designing web applications.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery

- MongoDB
- Express
- ReactJS
- Node.js

- Figma
- After Effects
- Premiere Pro
- Lightroom

## **EXPERIENCE**

**General Assembly, Remote** - Software Engineering Immersive

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

Three-month, 500-hour full-time and full-stack program conducted in a remote setting, providing experience with the latest front-end and back-end programming languages, tools, and methodologies including: HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript, jQuery, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Python, Django, NodeJS, ReactJS, Git, and Github.

Developed a portfolio of individually and collaboratively focused in-class projects, including:

- Movie Watch List/ Built with: MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js Watch Later
- Inventory Tracker/ Built with: MongoDB, Express, Node.js Nut Index

Christian Life Center, Tinley Park IL - Video Production Director

FEBRUARY 2016 - AUGUST 2019

Creative role recording and editing videos for ministry needs, traveled to other countries to record testimonial videos of ministry partners, and increased quality of content for the overall brand, trained and led a team of 30+ volunteers for a live broadcast. Tripled online audience in 6 months by increasing the quality of content and prioritizing SEO

- Video Examples <u>YouTube</u>
- Photography Examples <u>Instagram</u>

## **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly, Remote** - SEI

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

Software Engineering Immersive

Northern Oklahoma College, Tonkawa OK - AAS

AUGUST 2013 - MAY 2015

Major in Digital Media Animation & Design